{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Door Replacement \u0026 Repair Companies","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/61881/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":61881,"taskName":"Doors - Install or Repair","taskDescription":"Install or Repair Doors","xmTaskDescriptor":"Door Replacement \u0026 Repair Companies","matchable":false,"profileable":false,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":55,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Doors interior wood french entry","textMessagingName":"Inst Repr Door","rolloverLongDesc":"Includes door parts \u0026 opening, closing \u0026 latching mechanisms.","rolloverShortDesc":"Includes interior, exterior, garage, sliding, etc","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Install or Replace Interior Doors.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Door Replacement \u0026 Repair \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":22,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":39794,"bridgeTaskText":"Note: If your repair is not very complex or you have a variety of small projects, please ","bridgeTaskLinkText":"request a Handyman.","bridgeTaskLinkId":1437,"bridgeTaskActive":"Y","xmName":"Door Install or repair","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Doors - Install or Replace","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Door Project","urlName":"Door-Install-Repair","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Door Replacement \u0026 Repair Companies - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor","searchKeywords":"Doors,interior,wood,french,entry,latch,front,entry,double","emcCategoryOid":-12024,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":8285,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/61881/":{"taskOID":61881,"originalTaskOID":61881,"setID":8285,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":500741,"questionDisplayText":"Project Description","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What best describes this door project?","shortQuestionText":"What best describes this door project?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":203368,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Door installation / replacement","answerDisplayText":"Door installation / replacement","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203369,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Door repair","answerDisplayText":"Door repair","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502527,"questionDisplayText":"Type of door:","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of door project is this?","shortQuestionText":"What type of door project is this?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":2315,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Exterior","answerDisplayText":"Exterior","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3315,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Interior","answerDisplayText":"Interior","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5783,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Sliding","answerDisplayText":"Sliding","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203370,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Storm door","answerDisplayText":"Storm door","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2716,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Garage","answerDisplayText":"Garage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203372,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Glass shower door","answerDisplayText":"Glass shower door","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203373,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Secrurity gate","answerDisplayText":"Secrurity gate","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":8152,"questionDisplayText":"Is this an emergency?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is this an emergency?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502528,"questionDisplayText":"# of doors","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How many doors are included in this project?","shortQuestionText":"How many doors are included in this project?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10011,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"1","answerDisplayText":"1","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10012,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"2","answerDisplayText":"2","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10013,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"3","answerDisplayText":"3","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":473,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"4 or more","answerDisplayText":"4 or more","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":500741,"questionDisplayText":"Project Description","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What best describes this door project?","shortQuestionText":"What best describes this door project?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":203368,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Door installation / replacement","answerDisplayText":"Door installation / replacement","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203369,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Door repair","answerDisplayText":"Door repair","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":203368,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Door installation / replacement","answerDisplayText":"Door installation / replacement","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203369,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Door repair","answerDisplayText":"Door repair","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502527,"questionDisplayText":"Type of door:","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of door project is this?","shortQuestionText":"What type of door project is this?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":2315,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Exterior","answerDisplayText":"Exterior","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3315,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Interior","answerDisplayText":"Interior","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5783,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Sliding","answerDisplayText":"Sliding","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203370,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Storm door","answerDisplayText":"Storm door","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2716,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Garage","answerDisplayText":"Garage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203372,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Glass shower door","answerDisplayText":"Glass shower door","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203373,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Secrurity gate","answerDisplayText":"Secrurity gate","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":2315,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Exterior","answerDisplayText":"Exterior","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3315,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Interior","answerDisplayText":"Interior","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5783,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Sliding","answerDisplayText":"Sliding","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203370,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Storm door","answerDisplayText":"Storm door","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2716,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Garage","answerDisplayText":"Garage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203372,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Glass shower door","answerDisplayText":"Glass shower door","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203373,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Secrurity gate","answerDisplayText":"Secrurity gate","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":8152,"questionDisplayText":"Is this an emergency?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is this an emergency?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502528,"questionDisplayText":"# of doors","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How many doors are included in this project?","shortQuestionText":"How many doors are included in this project?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10011,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"1","answerDisplayText":"1","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10012,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"2","answerDisplayText":"2","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10013,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"3","answerDisplayText":"3","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":473,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"4 or more","answerDisplayText":"4 or more","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10011,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"1","answerDisplayText":"1","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10012,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"2","answerDisplayText":"2","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10013,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"3","answerDisplayText":"3","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":473,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"4 or more","answerDisplayText":"4 or more","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}